(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T22:51:28.486084",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです。
[Song: I Can't Say That I Like You]
こんなことになるなんて
That things would turn out like this...
出会う前に分かってたら
If I had known before we met,
もう少しだけしゃんとした僕を
I could have pulled myself together a bit more
見せれたはずなんだ
and showed you a better side of me.
どうしたらいいのかななんて
Wondering what I should do,
頭では分かってるけど
I know in my head, but...
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
At just a few casual words,
嬉しい顔が出ちゃって
a happy expression slipped onto my face.
こんなバレバレじゃ格好悪いな
It's so uncool being this obvious,
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな
but I can't back down like this.
でもいざ向かうと照れくさくて
Yet when I actually face you, I get so shy,
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't tell you that I like you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you.
浮き足だって空回り
Restless and getting nowhere,
何も言えずまたサヨナラ
unable to say anything, another goodbye.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I like you so much I can't help it.
明日こそは言えるかな
I wonder if I can say it tomorrow.
あなたも僕と同じように
If you were in love with me
恋してたら…なんて考えちゃうんだ
just like I am... I can't help thinking.
会えない日が続いてる
The days we can't meet keep continuing.
このままじゃよろしくない
Things can't go on like this.
会ったところで何ができるって
It's not like I can do much
わけじゃないんだけど
even if we met, though.
こんな恋は二度とないな
A love like this won't happen twice.
頭では分かってるけど
I know that in my head, but...
眩しすぎるその笑顔が
That smile of yours, so dazzling,
僕をあせらせるんだ
makes me feel flustered.
ずっと見ていたくなるような
Making me want to stare at you forever,
目をそらしたくなってしまうような
yet making me want to look away...
こんな気持ちわかるのかな
I wonder if you understand this feeling.
あなたが笑ってるならそれでいいんです
If you're smiling, then that's fine by me.
でも隣は僕がいいなあ
But I wish I was the one by your side.
もしかしたら実はずっと
Could it be that, truth is,
気づいてるんじゃないかな
you've noticed all along?
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I like you so much I can't help it.
言えるかな
I wonder if I can say it...
ドラマのキザなセリフは
Those sappy lines from dramas...
言えそうにないな
I don't think I can say them.
どうしたってこの気持ちは 抑えられそうにはないんだ
No matter what, it feels like I can't suppress these feelings.
あなたと出会ったあの日から ずっと気持ちは変わらないけど
Ever since the day I met you, my feelings haven't changed, but...
あなたのことが好きだなんて 言えないんです
I can't say that I like you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you...
空回りして空回り
Tripping over myself again and again,
何も言えずまたさようなら
unable to say anything, it's goodbye again.
あなたのことが好きすぎて たまらないんです
I like you so much I can't stand it.
明日こそは言いたいな
I want to say it tomorrow for sure.
あなたも僕と同じように
If you were in love with me too,
恋してたらなんて考えてる
just like I am with you... is what I'm thinking.
でもわかってる 考えすぎとのこと
But I know I'm just overthinking things.
Kobokobowa! Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hi everyone, kobokobowa!
こぼ・かなえるです！こぼの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
I'm Kobo Kanaeru! Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru 3D Birthday Stream 2025! ぱちぱちぱち！
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D Birthday Stream 2025! *Clap clap clap!*
How was Kobo's performance?
どうだった？またギターで出てきたよね？へへっ！
How was it? I came out playing the guitar again, right? Ehe!
えーっと、ちょっと待って...
Um, hold on a second...
Let me put the guitar down first.
よっしょ、よっしょ...
Up we go, alright...
オッケー！
Okay!
Once again, welcome to Kobo 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
こぼの3D生誕配信ようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an...
アイドルみたいなコンサート...テーマの...
idol-like concert themed...
3D birthday stream for about an hour,
with a lot of amazing and awesome guests! I bet you guys can't wait!
へっ？こぼ、おい！衣装が違ーう！
Huh? Hey Kobo, wait! The outfit is different!
Ah, chat! Nice eyes, chat! You noticed it! Yeah, you're right!
Look at Kobo's new stage!
でかい！新しいステージ！
It's huge! A new stage!
There's a big Cilus right here...
大きなチルす...
A big Cilus...
And so many stars! Stars! So many stars!
And then a big... a big rainbow right here!
Big, very big rainbow! And so many clouds, because...
A big, very big rainbow! And so many clouds, because...
I think it's just very aesthetic, yeah! And the floor!
Floor! 床見て！
The floor! Look at the floor!
わぁー！なんかパターン...海みたい！
Wow! The pattern... looks like the ocean!
You know? Yeah, like my hair!
So, don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay? Especially later!
Okay? Get a lot of screenshots!
And then post your comments, your moments, your impressions, your everything with the hashtag...
#3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS!
そしてこぼの3D生誕配信、SNSにハッシュタグ...
And for Kobo's 3D birthday stream, use the hashtag on SNS...
#3DKobornDay2025
をつけて、コメントと思い出、感想などなど投稿してね！
...and post your comments, memories, and impressions!
Right!
Are you guys ready for the next performance?
Okay, let me go to the next performance!
Okay, let's go to the next performance!
Wait, I try to remember...
Wait, I'm trying to remember...
あ、オッケー！覚えています！
Ah, okay! I remember!
それじゃ皆さん、準備いいかー？
Alright everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song!
とくべチュッして
Give me a special kiss!
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
一番大事がいい
I want to be your number one
君が作るオリジナルの
Give me your own original...
特別チュッして
...special kiss!
眩しくて 目が覚めて
It was so bright, I woke up
愛しく思ってよ
Please think of me fondly
眠り姫のように
Like Sleeping Beauty,
優しく口づけて
gently kiss my lips.
ドミネイトしたこの世界
In this world you dominate,
夕暮れかかる 君がいる
as dusk settles, you are here.
すべてに触れずに
Without touching anything else,
二人だけで居よう
let's just be the two of us.
私のこと 独占して
Monopolize me all for yourself,
君だけのものになってもいい？
can I become yours alone?
なんでもある日の
On an ordinary day,
なんでもないキッス見せて
show me a casual kiss.
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
ねえもっとギミー や Kiss も 私は
Hey, give me more, and kisses too, I...
君でいっぱいよ
...am filled with thoughts of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
A ribbon tied so tight it won't untie,
小指キュッて縛って
tied tightly around our pinkies.
そうよ一生 一生がいいの
Yes, forever—forever is what I want,
特別が欲しい
I want to be special.
二人きり週末は
On weekends with just the two of us,
奏でてよハーモニー
play our harmony.
流れ星見たら
If you see a shooting star,
私を思ってほしい
I want you to think of me.
甘々な君なのに
Even though you're so sweet,
白い街 吸い込まれ
absorbed into the white city,
誰かの姿に
toward someone else's shadow...
浮気はダメだね
Cheating is a big no-no!
好きなところ
The things I like about you,
優しいところ
your gentle side,
嫌いなところも優しいところ
the parts I dislike, and your gentle side too,
誰にもあげない
I won't give them to anyone,
私だけ一人占め
I want you all to myself.
だって今までの人と
Because unlike anyone before,
同じはいらないんです
I don't want the same old thing.
ねえもっとギミー Love 私のため
Hey, give me more love, live for my sake,
生きてほしいんです
that's what I want.
だからウサギと私は
So just like a rabbit,
寂しくさせないで
don't leave me feeling lonely.
束縛じゃないわ
It's not about restriction,
苦しいのが好き
I just like this painful feeling.
ショートケーキ
Strawberry shortcake,
いちごみたいに座ってもいい？
can I sit on top like a strawberry?
赤く甘い恋だもん
Because love is sweet and red.
誰があげた
Whoever gave you...
大好きも
...all those "I love you"s,
返してもらって全部私に
get them back and give them all to me,
頂戴 もっと
give them to me, even more!
君は神様が作る
You were created by God,
奇跡のような人
a person like a miracle.
ふれた顔もその寝顔も
Your touched face and your sleeping face too,
守ってあげるね
I will protect them for you.
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
ねえもっとギミー や Kiss も 私は
Hey, give me more, and kisses too, I...
君でいっぱいよ
...am filled with thoughts of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
A ribbon tied so tight it won't untie,
小指キュッて縛って
tied tightly around our pinkies.
ねえ baby 最初で最後の
Hey baby, make me your first and last...
特別にしてね
...special one.
天天天天天天天国 国国国国
Heaven heaven heaven heaven paradise!
オープンシステム
Open system!
天と地と人の交わるふぁんたじー
A fantasy where heaven, earth, and mankind intersect
今宵味わうさいけでりっく
Savoring the psychedelic tonight
踊り絡み合うどりあっく
Dancing and intertwining Doriak
恋のかけひきなたいぶれーく
A tie-break in love's bargaining
くだらない存在 身体を惹きたい
A foolish existence, wanting to attract the body
夢心地 触れ合い 惑わせたい
Dreamy touch, wanting to bewitch
曖昧
Ambiguity
色は甘い
The color is sweet,
鮮やかな赤い
a vivid red.
愛 見つめて限界
Staring at love to the limit,
月夜に誘われて
invited by the moonlit night.
天使と 悪魔と
Angels and demons,
angels and demons,
天使と 悪魔が
angels and demons
交錯した
intersected.
天国 地獄の
Heaven and hell's,
heaven and hell's,
天国 地獄の
heaven and hell's...
狭間で出会った
Met in the threshold between them.
天使と 悪魔と
Angels and demons,
angels and demons,
天使と 悪魔が
angels and demons
集って踊れば
gather and dance.
天国 地獄の
Heaven and hell's,
heaven and hell's...
門が開く
The gates open.
闇と光の交わるドラマチック
A dramatic intersection of darkness and light,
ほろ宵味わうサイケデリック
experiencing a slightly tipsy psychedelic feel.
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
Zodiac dancing and intertwining,
恋の駆け引きのダイブレイク
a daybreak of love's bargaining.
DEAD ALIVE
DEAD DEAD DEAD
BANG BANG BANG
DEAD ALIVE
DEAD DEAD BANG BANG
DEAD BANG
DEAD LET'S GO!
活けた魂をトレイに置いて
Placing arranged souls on a tray,
巡る迷宮の惑の揺れる炎
flickering flames in a spinning labyrinth.
先にあなたが魅了したなら
If you were captivated first,
もう迷わない グラス飲み干して
I won't hesitate anymore, drain your glass.
今夜オールイン 降りないこの勝負
All in tonight, not backing down from this match.
今 天国と地獄をつなぐ門が開いている
Now, the gate connecting Heaven and Hell is open.
天使と悪魔 使者と聖者が入り乱れ
Angels and demons, emissaries and saints intermingle,
踊り 笑い すべては混沌の中に呑み込まれていく
dancing, laughing, all being swallowed into chaos.
それは世界の終焉であり 新たなる始まりでもあるのだった
It was the end of the world, and also a new beginning.
DEAD ALIVE
DEAD DEAD DEAD
BANG BANG BANG
DEAD ALIVE
DEAD DEAD BANG BANG
DEAD BANG
天 天 天 天
Ten, ten, ten, ten,
天国 天
Heaven, heaven,
天 天 天 天
Ten, ten, ten, ten,
天国 地獄
Heaven, hell!
天 天 天 天
Ten, ten, ten, ten,
天国 天
Heaven, heaven,
天 天 天 天
Ten, ten, ten, ten,
天国 地獄
Heaven, hell!
月夜に誘われ
Invited by the moonlit night,
天使と 悪魔と
angels and demons,
天使と 悪魔が
angels and demons
交錯した
intersected.
天国 地獄の
Heaven and hell's...
骨格消えない 果てない むなしい
Unfading structure, endless, empty,
天国 地獄の
Heaven and hell's,
heaven and hell's...
狭間で出会った
Met in the threshold between them.
天使と 悪魔と
Angels and demons,
angels and demons,
天使と 悪魔が
angels and demons
集って踊れば
gather and dance.
天国 地獄の
Heaven and hell's,
heaven and hell's,
天国 地獄の
heaven and hell's...
狭間で出会った
Met in the threshold between them.
天使と 悪魔と
Angels and demons,
angels and demons,
天使と 悪魔が
angels and demons
集って踊れば
gather and dance.
DANCE DANCE DANCE DANCE
DEAD ALIVE
DEAD DEAD DEAD
天国 地獄
Heaven, hell!
DEAD ALIVE
DEAD DEAD BANG BANG
天国 地獄
Heaven, hell!
やばい！
Oh crap!
Iblis dari mana?
Where is this demon from?
Wah, gatal ini orang. Iblis, wah...
Wow, this person's so annoying. Demon, woah...
Itu 4 tanduk, bahaya sekali, sebal sekali.
Those four horns, super dangerous, super annoying.
Ya, jadi gini.
Yeah, so it's like this.
Aku datang jauh-jauh... Ya, jauh-jauh...
I came from so far away... Yeah, so far away...
Apa? Meskipun tidak diundang...
What? Even though I wasn't invited...
Oh, ini diundang.
Oh, you were invited.
Iya, kayaknya kamu ngundang yang lain deh tadi.
Yeah, looks like you invited someone else earlier.
Maksudnya? No, I mean...
What do you mean? No, I mean...
Kenapa tiba-tiba Nihongo?
Why are you suddenly speaking Japanese?
Kamu malaikat Japan, ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa pusing muter-muter enggak pusing.
How can you spin around without getting dizzy?
Pusing, kan?
You are dizzy, right?
Malaikat kok pusing, guys.
How can an angel get dizzy, guys?
Iya, aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya.
Yeah, I'm here actually just to flirt with you.
Pengen main bareng, pengen godain kamu aja.
I wanted to hang out together, just wanted to tease you.
Sini, sini, sini, sini!
Come here, come here, come here, come here!
Ada jidat.
There's a forehead.
Pulang, kamu habis ini... Loh, kamu habis ini pulang sama aku, kan?
Go home, after this you... Wait, after this you're going home with me, right?
Pulang?
Go home?
Iya, habis ini enggak ada apa-apa lagi, kan?
Yeah, there's nothing else after this, right?
Ngapain? Enak-enak aku di atas.
For what? I'm enjoying myself up here.
Masa kamu mau nyeret aku?
Don't tell me you want to drag me down?
Loh, loh, bukannya kita...
Wait, aren't we...
Kita, kita, kita... Raja Iblis!
We, we, we... Demon King!
Ajak, dong. Ajak, dong, banget.
Invite me, then. Definitely invite me.
Kamu saya ajak...
I'm inviting you...
Aku kesepian.
I'm lonely.
Ayo sini!
Come on, over here!
Fallen angel, nih!
A fallen angel!
Enggak, enggak ada fallen angel, ya guys.
No, there's no fallen angel, guys.
Saktinya aku panah.
With my magic, I shoot an arrow.
Iya, iya, coba, coba.
Yeah, yeah, try it, try it.
Satu, dua, tiga... Pugh!
One, two, three... Pow!
Iya, iya! Wah, gila, gila, gila!
Yeah, yeah! Wow, crazy, crazy, crazy!
How to tame your demon.
Jadi Light Novel.
It becomes a Light Novel.
Gimana tadi freestyle kita? Keren banget ya, guys?
How was our freestyle earlier? It was super cool, right guys?
Iya, lucu enggak, guys?
Yeah, wasn't it cute, guys?
Atas! Bawah!
Up! Down!
Atas! Bawah! Atas!
Up! Down! Up!
Tapi pas kamu atas, aku bawah.
But when you went up, I went down.
Kebalik! Sama aja.
Reversed! It's the same thing.
Tau ya, orang mah kebalik kiri-kanan.
You know, usually people reverse left and right.
Dia kebalik... Tetep atas!
She reversed... Still up!
Atas! Aku bawah. Atas!
Up! I'm down. Up!
Kocak, kocak.
So funny, so funny.
Ya udah.
Alright then.
Ya udah kalau gitu, aku... aku wanita sibuk ya sebenarnya. Jadi kayak...
Alright then, I'm... I'm actually a busy woman. So like...
...gak gitu banyak waktu. Aku di sini mampir...
...I don't have that much time. I'm just stopping by...
Bullshit!
Mampir dikit aja bentaran.
Just stopping by briefly for a bit.
Bullshit! Pemimpin DeGoku nih!
Bullshit! She's the leader of DeGoku!
Asik!
Awesome!
Oke.
Okay.
Baik. Fiksi ya, guys. Ini cerita fiksi, jangan ditiru ya, guys.
Alright. It's fiction, guys. This is a fictional story, don't imitate it, guys.
Fiksi, fiksi ya, guys.
Fiction, it's fiction, guys.
Sensitif ini, sensitif! Fiksi, bohongan.
This is sensitive, sensitive! Fiction, fake.
Oke kalau gitu, bye!
Okay then, bye!
Nggak mau! Ikut aku aja!
No way! Just come with me!
Enggak! Jagain nih anaknya, guys!
No! Watch over this kid, guys!
Kita lihat perilakunya...
Let's see her behavior...
...beneran seisho apa enggak.
...whether she's actually seisho or not.
Lihat tuh bajunya. Jagain, jagain! Ya udah, bye!
Look at her clothes. Watch over her, watch over her! Alright, bye!
Bye!
Bisa jadi fallen angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I might become a fallen angel because of her instigation, guys.
Gak jelas!
Makes no sense!
させる恋の味
Make them fall in love with the taste
何とかしなくちゃならなくて
I have to do something about it
突然メイドになっちゃって
Suddenly I became a maid
いつものようにお店の掃除
Cleaning the shop like always
トビラ開いちゃって目が合った？
The door opened and our eyes met?
何だか忙しくなっちゃって
Somehow I got so busy
あ慌てんぼうにもなっちゃって…
And I even became a scatterbrain...
お仕事中に！推しに夢中に！
In the middle of work! Obsessed with my fave!
どこを探しても見当当たらないじゃん！
No matter where I look, I can't find it!
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
もういいよ！
Ready!
秘密だよね？
It's a secret, right?
もういいの？
Is it really okay?
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen for you
ねぇ、好きって言って！！
Hey, tell me you love me!!
♡どきどきキュン！♡ 送るラブビーム
♡Dokidoki kyun!♡ Sending a love beam
君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's the magic that makes you fall for me
ほら♡どきどきキュン！♡ わたし大暴走…
Look, ♡dokidoki kyun!♡ I'm going totally wild...
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you fall for me
もう君にキュン！♡ わたし大妄想
Already head over heels for you! ♡ My wild delusions
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん！
It's magic that lets us fall in love together!
だから君がキュン！ってなる恋になって…
So fall in love with a heart-pounding passion...
一つどうぞ これが恋の味！
Here, have one, this is the taste of love!
楽しくて仕方なくたって
Even if it's so much fun I can't help it
そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
It's almost coming to an end
会いたくなって 落ち込んじゃって
Wanting to see you, feeling down
君とぶつかって目が合った！
Bumping into you and our eyes met!
何度も会いたくなっちゃって
Wanting to see you over and over again
今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
Today alone isn't enough
計画通り！ わたしの勝利！
Just as planned! My victory!
君に会いたくて仕方がないよ
I just can't help wanting to see you
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
君だけだよ？
It's only you, you know?
もうずっと愛し合いたいよ
I want us to love each other forever
ねぇ、好きって言って！！
Hey, tell me you love me!!
どきどきキュン 君にラブビーム
Dokidoki kyun, a love beam to you
2人夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic that lets the two of us fall in love
ほら どきどきキュン わたし大恋愛…
Look, dokidoki kyun, my grand romance...
君を夢中にさせる恋の巻
The chapter of love that makes you fall for me
もう君にキュン わたし大混乱
Already head over heels for you, I'm super confused
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん！
It's magic that lets us fall in love together!
だから君はキュン！ってなる恋に落ちて、
So fall into a heart-pounding love,
一つどうぞ これが恋の味！
Here, have one, this is the taste of love!
もうこのままだったら
If things stay like this
ここで会うこともなくなって
We won't even meet here anymore
もう君の声が聞きやすくなるの
And I'll want to hear your voice even more
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
もういいの？
Is it really okay?
秘密なのに？
Even though it's a secret?
もういいよ
It's okay now
このまま好きになってく
Falling for you more and more
好きって言って！！
Tell me you love me!!
どきどきキュン 送るラブビーム
Dokidoki kyun, sending a love beam
君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's magic that makes you fall for me
ほら どきどきキュン わたし大暴走
Look, dokidoki kyun, I'm going totally wild
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you fall for me
もう君にキュン わたし大妄想
Already head over heels for you, my wild delusions
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん！
It's magic that lets us fall in love together!
だから君がキュン！ってなる恋になって…
So fall in love with a heart-pounding passion...
一つどうぞ これが恋の味！
Here, have one, this is the taste of love!
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Banget udah mau ngelag, tapi...
It's starting to lag a lot, but...
...masih pada semangat gak semuanya?
...is everyone still hyped up?
なあ、たくさんゲストとパフォーマンスしてから
Hey, after performing with so many guests,
次は、コボはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います。
next, Kobo wants to sing alone again!
これから歌うこの曲は、最近コボが気に入ってる曲で
This song I'm about to sing is one I've been really into lately,
聴いたら幸せな気持ちになりました。
and listening to it made me feel so happy.
皆さんも
I hope all of you,
この曲聴いて、幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
upon listening to this song, can feel happy too.
それでは、次の曲
Now then, the next song...
青山テルマさんの
by Teruma Aoyama...
Happinessです！
Happiness!
きっと happiness 君がいれば
I'm sure of happiness, as long as you're here,
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I can believe that everything will be fine.
何も言わなくても
Even if nothing is said,
感じてる You're the one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me.
Oh oh oh...
You always make me happy
落ち込んで 眠れなくて
Feeling down and unable to sleep,
君との写真 見つめている
I'm staring at photos of us together.
いくつもの 笑顔たちに
Saved by all those smiling faces,
助けられるよ My life
my life is supported.
ずっと一緒だよ
We'll always be together,
泣いてもいいよ
it's okay to cry.
あの涙を抱きしめてくれた
You held me tight through those tears.
どこにいるの？
"Where are you?"
ここにいるから
"I'm right here,"
すぐに会いたくて
wanting to see you right away...
きっと happiness 君がいれば
I'm sure of happiness, as long as you're here,
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I can believe that everything will be fine.
何も言わなくても
Even if nothing is said,
感じてる You're the one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me.
君と happiness
Happiness with you,
どんなときも
no matter when,
ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ
I believe I'm not alone.
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow,
歩けるね
I can keep walking,
Please stay by my side
君に出会えてからは
Ever since I met you,
素直に笑っていられるよ
I've been able to smile honestly.
少しずつ自分のこと
Little by little,
好きになった For your love
I came to like myself, for your love.
そう 今なら
Yes, now,
ねぇ 心から
hey, from the bottom of my heart,
分かり合えるって思えるよ
I feel like we can truly understand each other.
強がらずに
Without acting tough,
ありのままでも見つめてくれた
you looked at me just as I am.
だから happiness 君のことを
That's why, happiness, I want to know you
今よりももっと知りたくて
even more than I do now.
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words,
大切な You're the one for me
you're my precious one for me.
私にも君に
I want to do
何かできることをしたいよ
something for you too.
いつでも一緒だから
Because we're always together,
守っていけるから ずっと
I can protect you, forever.
ずっと...
Forever...
きっと happiness 君がいれば
I'm sure of happiness, as long as you're here,
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I can believe that everything will be fine.
何も言わなくても
Even if nothing is said,
感じてる You're the one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me.
君と happiness
Happiness with you,
どんなときも
no matter when,
ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ
I believe I'm not alone.
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow,
歩けるね
I can keep walking,
Please stay by my side
大切な You're the one for me
You're my precious one for me.
Let's go!
Oh oh oh... You always make me happy
Oh oh oh...
Smile for me baby
Nah nah nah nah nah
You always make me happy
Oh oh oh...
Smile for me baby
Oh oh oh... You always make me happy
ようこそお越しなさったご主人様 隣に座ってせーの
Welcome, master! Take a seat right beside me, ready...
萌え 萌え 萌え 萌え
Moe, moe, moe, moe!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ ねぇ教えて 笑顔で up pull pull
Who's actually going to be happy with this? Hey, tell me, with a smile, up pull pull!
愛想は逸れてご苦労様 私とあなたでせーの
Thanks for putting up with losing your cool, you and I, ready...
luv luv luv luv
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ ねぇ教えて 笑顔で up pull pull
Who's actually going to be happy with this? Hey, tell me, with a smile, up pull pull!
ひらりはらり女の子
Fluttering, fluttering, a girl...
ふわりふわり言葉のsaw
Softly, softly, a saw of words...
それってつまりお冷めな娘 感情的リアル 笑顔で up pull pull
That means, in short, a cool girl, emotionally real, with a smile, up pull pull!
人は見かけによらぬもの
Appearances can be deceiving,
嘘を嘘とは見抜けない
you can't tell a lie from the truth.
したたかな袖飾りの革
Clever leather sleeve cuffs,
鳥肌 鮫肌 アンドゥ トロワ
goosebumps, shark skin, un, deux, trois!
間違ったご指名をいただきます 私とあなたでせーの
I'll take the wrong nomination, you and I, ready...
luv luv luv luv
これは派手にご苦労様 遊びましょう 笑顔で up brrrt brrrt
Thanks for your lavish hard work, let's play, with a smile, up brrrt brrrt!
ひらりはらりここは何処
Fluttering, fluttering, where are we?
ふわりふわり査討 let me show
Softly, softly, inspecting, let me show...
それってつまりお冷めな娘 確証的リアル 笑顔で up brrrt brrrt
That means, in short, a cool girl, demonstratively real, with a smile, up brrrt brrrt!
歌い出す秘密の鐘
The secret bell starts to sing...
終わる事の無いこの世界
In this world with no end...
悲しい子供は
Sad children...
虚しい子供は
Empty children...
眠らせて
Put them to sleep...
おままごと 遊びましょう
Playing house, let's play,
笑顔で up pull pull
with a smile, up pull pull!
ひらりはらり女の子
Fluttering, fluttering, a girl...
ふわりふわり言葉のsaw
Softly, softly, a saw of words...
それってつまりお冷めな娘 感情的リアル 笑顔で up pull pull
That means, in short, a cool girl, emotionally real, with a smile, up pull pull!
遊びましょう 笑顔で up pull pull
Let's play, with a smile, up pull pull!
up pull pull
Let's dance with me!
何回でもかける true magic
Casting true magic again and again!
まだまだ今日は夢心地
Today is still like a dream!
眠たくても簡単再現
Even if you're sleepy, it's easy to recreate!
何度でも「おかえり」って once again
Saying "welcome back" again and again, once again!
朝が来るその時まで
Until the morning comes...
ねぇ僕とどうだい？
Hey, how about joining me?
塞ぎ込んでる週の終わり退屈そうだけどどうだろう 誘っていいかな
You look bored at the end of a gloomy week, but how about it? Can I invite you out?
かも分かんない
Maybe, who knows?
どっち向いてる？ こっち向いてる？ あっち向いてホイ！なんかじゃなくて キミのことだもん もっとちゃんと話聞いてよ
Where are you looking? Looking this way? Not playing "look over there!", I'm talking about you! Listen to me more carefully!
劣勢から逆転？
A reversal from a disadvantage?
昨日より今日の方が可愛いし 居ても立ってもいられない
Today is cuter than yesterday, I just can't stand still!
聞こえる0時告げるチャイム
Hearing the chime toll midnight,
時間切れの先へ
beyond time's limit...
飛び出して
Leaping out!
駆け出して
Running forward!
まだまだ夜終われない
The night isn't over yet!
こんな最高な日々が 明日も続いていくなら
If these amazing days keep continuing tomorrow as well...
ねぇキミはどうだい？
Hey, how about you?
待ち望んでるキミの理想の お姫様の席をどうしよう 狙っていいかな
What should we do about the seat for your ideal princess that you've been waiting for? Can I aim for it?
Make a chance! Let's dance!
え、今じゃない？！
Wait, not now?!
猫も杓子も曲に合わせて
Everyone and their mother, matching the song...
ステップなんか踏んでみてご機嫌そう
Try stepping to it and look so cheerful!
昨日より今日がずっと楽しくて 続けたいときには
When today is way more fun than yesterday and you want it to keep going...
聞こえる0時告げるチャイム
Hearing the chime toll midnight,
時間切れの先へ
beyond time's limit...
終わらない
It won't end!
止まらない
It won't stop!
まだまだ夜長いから
Because the night is still long!
こんな最高な...
Such a supreme...
リズムに
To the rhythm,
体をあずけてみたら
if you surrender your body,
ほら 魔法みたい
look, it's like magic!
騒がしくて新しくなってフライハイ 毎日がいい
It's noisy and fresh, fly high, every day is great!
魔法なんてありえない でも今夜だけは現実になるかも
Magic can't exist, but maybe tonight it'll become reality.
心揺らせ 音に乗って踊れ君も
Sway your heart, dance to the music, you too!
終わらない夜に とびきりの魔法を
On this endless night, a special magic...
君にも かけてあげるから 僕の手をとってよ
I'll cast it on you too, so take my hand!
鳴り止まないミュージック 魔法が解けるまで 最高で最強な夜が今日も更けていく
Non-stop music, until the magic fades, tonight deepens into the best and strongest night!
こんな夢みたいな日々が 明日も続いていくなら ねぇ君は
If days like a dream like this continue tomorrow, hey, what about you?
アンコール 大胆に夜を飾るソング 何回でもかける呪文 まだまだ続く夢心地
Encore! A song boldly decorating the night, a spell cast over and over, this dreamy bliss goes on!
嘘みたいだけど 朝が来るそのときまで ねぇ僕と踊ろう
It feels unbelievable, but until the morning comes, hey, dance with me!
うわー！ ここどこー？
Woah! Where are we?
わかんないー！
I don't know!
え、なんか雲おいしそうじゃない？
Huh, doesn't that cloud look delicious?
食べてみようよ！
Let's eat it!
おいしいー！
Yummy!
Delicious!
あっちゃっちゃっ... 何？
Wait... what?
何をしてるのー？
What are you doing?
あ！ こぼー！ こぼちゃーん！
Ah! Kobo! Kobo-chan!
あん！ 初めは食べてないです！
Ah! I didn't eat it at first!
見守ってた！ 見守ってた！ 初めは食べてないです！
I was just watching! I didn't eat it at first!
私の雲〜！
My clouds~!
えー、誰が...
Umm, who...
初めは食べてない！
We didn't eat it at first!
ちゃちゃもにゃ！
No excuses!
こぼじゃないんだよ！ 何をしてるのー？
It wasn't me! What are you doing?
Oh, calm down! Today is your birthday!
え、ちょ... 誕生日！ Happy birthday!
Eh, wait... Birthday! Happy birthday!
あーっ！ あ、ありがとー！
Ah! Thank you!
Happy birthday! Welcome, welcome! 今日はお祝い！
Happy birthday! Welcome, welcome! Today is a celebration!
えー、じゃあ、先輩達と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
Umm, then I want to sing and dance together with my senpais!
歌って踊りたい！
Sing and dance!
OK, OK, OK!
こぼの振り付け！
Kobo's choreography!
Very nice! Very, very nice!
そうそう！ こぼ先生と呼んでください！
Yes, yes! Please call me Teacher Kobo!
こぼちゃん！
Kobo-chan!
あ、ガキだからダメ！
Ah, treating me like a kid is no good!
じゃあ、勉強した？ もちろん！
So, did you practice? Of course!
あ、バッチリ！ こぼ先輩、これ振り付け？
Ah, perfect! Kobo-senpai, is this choreography?
いや、これ choreography!
No, this is choreography!
じゃあ、行きましょう！
Then let's listen!
イエス！ 行きましょう！ OK! Let's go!
Yes! Let's go! OK! Let's go!
おー、いいね！ ポジションOK？
Oh, nice! Position OK?
OK! ポジションOK！
OK! Position OK!
OK, OK, じゃあ行きましょう！
OK, OK, then let's go!
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
[Title: Honeymoon Un Deux Trois]
誰もいなくなった 二人だけの街に
In the town where everyone has gone, leaving just the two of us,
機械仕掛けの時計が 夜の訪れ知らせる
the clockwork clock signals the arrival of night.
夕闇が空を ワイン色に染めて
The twilight dyes the sky in the color of wine,
不慣れな二人を 舞台へと誘う
inviting the unaccustomed pair onto the stage.
chasse 'n' whisk 'n' natural-turn あなたに魔法をあげる
Chasse 'n' whisk 'n' natural-turn, I'll grant you magic,
throwaway and oversway その名前は honey mead
throwaway and oversway, its name is honey mead.
蜜月 un ・ deux ・ trois 互いの指を絡めて
Honeymoon un, deux, trois, interlocking our fingers,
Singin' swingin' sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our shared dream.
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural-Turn
貴方に魔法をかける
I'll cast a spell upon you.
Throwaway and Oversway
魅惑の蜜 honey mead
Captivating honey mead.
蜜月 Un・Deux・Trois
Honeymoon 1, 2, 3
その唇を重ねて
Bringing our lips together,
Singin' swingin' sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love.
月明かりが路地を
Moonlight illuminates the alleyway,
黄金色に照らして
in a golden glow.
幼い二人は
The young pair of us
躓きながら踊る
dance as we stumble along.
蜜月 Un・Deux・Trois
Honeymoon 1, 2, 3
互いの指を絡めて
Intertwining our fingers,
Singin' swingin' sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our shared dream.
蜜月 Un・Deux・Trois
Honeymoon 1, 2, 3
その唇を重ねて
Bringing our lips together,
Singin' swingin' sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love.
楽しかったー！
That was so fun!
やったー！
Yay!
ダンス上手！ダンス上手！
Great dancing! So good at dancing!
なんか、スワン！
Like... a swan!
こぼ先輩もスワン！
Kobo-senpai is a swan too!
スワン！かなでもスワン！
Swan! Kanade is also a swan!
スワン！
Swan!
ビューティフルスワン！
Beautiful swan!
めっちゃエレガント！
So elegant!
これ、振り付け二人が作ってくれました！
These two made the choreography!
難しかった！
It was hard!
立派！えらいえらい！
Splendid! Good job, good job!
いや、簡単ですし！簡単だよ！
No, it was easy! Easy peasy!
楽しかった！
That was fun!
来てくれてありがとうね！
Thank you for coming!
こぼ先輩、呼んでくれてありがとう！
Kobo-senpai, thank you for inviting us!
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがとう！
Thank you so much for dancing with me!
いつでも任せてー！
You can count on us anytime!
いつでも、いつでも！
Anytime, anytime!
ハッピーバースデー！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ファイトー！
Do your best!
じゃあ、バイバーイ！
Well then, bye-bye!
みんな帰っちゃった…
Everyone left...
寂しい…悲しい…
I'm lonely... Sad...
誰も来ないのかな…
Is no one else coming...?
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye.
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
Make me forget after goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない 離せない 戻りたい
Can't stay apart, can't let go, I want to go back.
Take me free この体は君がいた
Take me free, this body had you in it.
止まった色のみ
Only in stagnant colors,
部屋の中は香水だらけに染めた ジルスチュアートのフレーバー
the room is dyed in perfume, with the scent of Jill Stuart.
当たり前さえも奇跡 触れ合えない君との軌跡
Even the ordinary was a miracle; the path shared with you, whom I cannot touch.
どれだけ恋しても 超えられない君を
No matter how much I fall in love, I cannot reach beyond you...
今なら分かる気がして
I feel like I can understand now...
今から過去に戻れるなら
If I could return to the past right now...
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye,
サヨナラの後（あと）は 忘れさせて
and after goodbye, let me forget.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I can't leave,
離せない
I can't let go,
戻りたい
I want to go back,
Take me free
ほど解きたいほど 愛しているのよ
I love you so much that I want to unravel it all.
気づけばあなたのことばかり浮かべて
Before I know it, my mind is filled only with thoughts of you.
明日になれば大丈夫
If tomorrow comes, I'll be alright.
何度と言い聞かせればいいの
How many times must I keep convincing myself?
愛という沼に 溺れている
I'm drowning in the swamp called love.
私の声は 届かない
My voice doesn't reach you.
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye,
サヨナラの後（あと）は 忘れさせて
and after goodbye, let me forget.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I can't leave,
離せない
I can't let go,
戻りたい
I want to go back,
Take me free
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye,
サヨナラの後（あと）は 忘れさせて
and after goodbye, let me forget.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I can't leave,
離せない
I can't let go,
戻れない
I can't turn back,
Take me free
かえれない日々 抱きしめたまま いつか そう いつか
Holding close those days I cannot return to, someday... yes, someday...
弱い心が 捕まる前に そっと あなたを遠ざけた
Before my weak heart gets caught, I quietly pushed you away.
あぁ こんな気持ち
Ah, feeling like this...
つらすぎるよ もう
...is just too painful now.
あなたは 誰なの？
Who are you?
どこに 隠れていたの？
Where were you hiding?
ひろく 怯えている
Frightened in this vast space,
うつむいたままの
with my head cast down...
いや だから わたしが
No... that's why I...
であっていた
...met you.
またあの季節 夜空は白く
That season again, the night sky turns white,
あなたもいて
and you are there too.
ふれてこないで 嬉しいけど
Don't touch me... even though I'm happy,
心が痛い... 痛い
my heart aches... it aches.
離したくない 離れたくない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to leave,
でもあきらめてた
but I had given up.
もうこれ以上 好きになれない
I can't love you any more than this,
失う痛み 耐えきれないよ
I can't bear the pain of losing you.
かえれない日々 抱きしめたまま
Holding close those days I cannot return to,
いつか そう いつか
someday... yes, someday...
ただ側にいて それだけでいい
Just stay by my side, that is enough,
素直にはなれないけれど
even if I can't be honest with you.
さあ 顔を上げて
Come on, lift up your head
歩み始めなきゃ
and start walking forward.
リアルな私を
Notice the real me,
気づいて
pay attention to me.
またあの季節 この空の下 見上げている
Once again in that season, under this sky, I'm looking up.
傷ついたもの もう元には 戻らないけど
What was hurt will never go back to the way it was, but...
離したくない 離れたくない もう諦めない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to be apart, I won't give up anymore.
あなたの心 傷つけてでも この気持ち
Even if it hurts your heart, this feeling...
嘘つけない いつか笑顔で 話せるような
I cannot lie. So that one day we can talk with a smile,
私を見つけて
please find me.
傍に居て 聞かせてほしい
Stay by my side, I want you to tell me...
二度と一人にはしないと
that you'll never leave me alone again.
変えられない日々 抱きしめたまま
Embracing the unchangeable days,
きっとそう きっと
surely, yes, surely...
あの日の気持ち 受け止めないと 前に進むことができない
If I don't accept the feelings of that day, I can't move forward.
離したくない 離れたくない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to be apart.
一つになれない
Even if we can't become one,
大好きだよと 伝えたいだけ
I just want to tell you that I love you.
ホント 素直じゃないけれど
Honestly, I'm not very honest, but...
So, how is it, guys?
The last closing... Did you take a lot of screenshots?
And ah, how about my new stage?
Look! Wow, it's very cloudy here.
Yeah, as you can see, there's two big Chillus on the left and right.
So cute! みんなどうだった？こぼのパフォーマンス。
So cute! How was everyone? Kobo's performance.
いっぱいスクショ取れたかな？
Did you get to take lots of screenshots?
こぼの新しいステージはもうどうだった？可愛いでしょ？ビッグチルズがありますのでめちゃ可愛いよね！
How was Kobo's new stage? Cute, right? Having the Big Chillus makes it super cute, doesn't it?
So actually, yeah, we're already at the end of the show, guys.
そろそろお別れ時間になりますよ。
It's almost time to say goodbye.
But don't worry! Kobo still has something to share with you guys.
まだ皆さんにお知らせがあります！
I still have an announcement for everyone!
じゃじゃーん！
Tada!
Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set!
This time, Kobo's birthday merch theme is Jellyfish...
Princess...
I wanted to wear a jellyfish costume for a long time,
and finally, my wish came true.
So, how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful?
And the KV is drawn by Sukotti-sensei.
Sukotti-sensei, ありがとう！ありがとう！
Sukotti-sensei, thank you! Thank you!
And, as you wish, guys...
Finally, ta-da!
Kobokers' Happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers and perfect for cheering me during events.
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers, perfect for cheering me during events.
Keren banget! Happi, happi, happi! Come on, buy happi, happi!
It's so cool! Happi, happi, happi! Come on, buy happi, happi!
And if you look closely, this happi design is like... it's like my raincoat, right?
And you can see there's two of us in the front, and me in the back. Right?
And next, we have this Jellyfish Princess on the Wall tapestry!
It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration. It's super high quality and perfect for decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smirk face every morning.
And also don't forget to praise the Lord every day!
Then look at this! The "Jellyfish Princess, you got this" button badge set! Two pieces.
One has my birthday outfit, and the other is an illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself. It looks good, right?
Do you like it? I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag, or your hat, or your heart.
Okay, so this one is one of my favorites.
One, two, three... Ta-da! The plushie keychain!
It's me, but mini Kobo! In mini form!
You can bring me anywhere: on your backpack, your keys, your motorcycle, the car, whatever!
Even next to your computer while you watch my streams.
So soft and squishy!
And finally, we also have the situational voice pack!
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess". What does it mean?!
Buy it, buy it, okay? So you know what does it mean.
Buy it, buy it, okay? So you know what it means.
It'll be a special voice pack where I talk to you about Jellyfish Princess and, you know, your one and only, just for you.
Yeah, don't miss out my birthday merch, guys.
Yeah, don't miss out on my birthday merch, guys.
If you buy a set of them, you'll get a special bromide with my signature on it.
The merch is available for a limited time only, so you can grab yours...
...from the official shop. Links are in the description.
So, yeah! That's all for the announcement.
Thank you all for coming and watching Kobo's performance today.
以上、グッズとお知らせでした。
That's all for the merchandise and announcements.
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので、クリックしてね。
Links are provided in the description and chat section, so please click them.
Ah, but I can hear some of you want an encore.
アンコール欲しい？
Do you want an encore?
じゃあ、しょうがないわ。
Well then, I guess I have no choice.
Please listen, Sweet Memories.
Please listen to "Sweet Memories".
Sweet Memories
作詞：松本隆 / 作曲：大村雅朗
[Song: Sweet Memories
Lyrics: Takashi Matsumoto / Music: Masaaki Omura]
なつかしい 痛みだわ
It's a nostalgic pain...
ずっと前に 忘れていた
I had forgotten it long ago.
でも あなたを見たとき
But when I saw you,
時間だけ 後戻りしたの
time alone turned backward.
「幸福？」と 聞かないで
Don't ask me, "Are you happy?"
嘘つくのは 上手じゃない
I'm not good at lying.
友達なら いるけど
I have friends,
あんなには 燃えあがれなくて
but I can't burn with passion like back then.
失った 夢だけが 美しく 見えるのは なぜかしら
Why is it that only lost dreams look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Even the kindness of days gone by is now...
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
sweet memories, sweet memories.
Don't kiss me baby we can never be
So don't add more pain, please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many nights thinking of you
Longing for your touch, I have once loved you so much
あの頃は 若すぎて
Back then, we were too young,
いたずらに 傷つけあった 二人
hurting each other needlessly.
色褪せた 哀しみも 今は
Even faded sadness is now...
遠い記憶 Sweet memories
a distant memory, sweet memories.
失った 夢だけが 美しく 見えるのは なぜかしら
Why is it that only lost dreams look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Even the kindness of days gone by is now...
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
sweet memories, sweet memories.
フィナーレ。
[Title: Finale.]
君はほんとに わかってないよ
You really don't understand at all.
例えば ハッピー
For example, a happy
エンドより 甘くて 豪華な
ending, or a dessert sweeter and more luxurious,
デザートより 君がいいんだよ
I'd rather have you.
ふたつの傘より 相合傘
Rather than two separate umbrellas, sharing one,
ちょっと冷たいけど
it's a little cold, but
愛するための 代償ならいくらでも
if it's the price for loving you, I'd pay any amount,
でもどうぞ ただずっとそばにいたい
so please, I just want to stay by your side forever.
ねえ 誰も星くずもない ふたりぼっちの世界で ずっと
Hey, in a world with no star dust, just the two of us alone, forever...
最後の花火をあげて フィナーレを飾って
Let's launch the final fireworks and adorn the finale,
奇跡のフリ 恋に落ちて
pretend it's a miracle, fall in love,
誰も離さないで
and don't let anyone go.
味気ない世界も悪くないね
A dull world isn't so bad either, is it?
どんなに恋をしたって 出逢えないよ きっと
No matter how much I fall in love, I surely won't find another,
終わりもない 幸せにキスをしよう
there's no end, so let me kiss this happiness.
いつか今日を 忘れても
Even if I forget today productively someday,
君がいいんだよ
I'd still want you,
天気が雨の日
On a rainy day,
愛して 初めて目が合った
loving you, our eyes met for the first time.
ねえ 誰も星くずもない ふたりぼっちの世界で ずっと
Hey, in a world with no star dust, just the two of us alone, forever...
最後の花火をあげて フィナーレを誓って
Let's launch the final fireworks and swear to the finale,
奇跡のフリ 恋に落ちて
pretend it's a miracle, fall in love,
誰も離さないで
and don't let anyone go.
そっけない世界も悪くないね
A cold world isn't so bad either, is it?
どんなに恋をしたって 忘れられないの
No matter how much I fall in love, I can't forget,
終わりもない 幸せにキスをしよう
there's no end, so let me kiss this happiness.
味気ないね
It's dull, isn't it?
でもそれがね
But you know, that's...
ふたりの幸せ
our happiness.
Oh, I almost cried! I almost cried singing this song.
Thank you for today, guys! Thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta, it's because she covered this finale song first, and then I was inspired, so yeah.
And thank you to Zeta, because she covered this finale song first, and then I was inspired, so yeah.
Aku belajar lagunya dari sini.
I learned the song from her.
今日は来てくれて、最後まで見てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today and watching until the end!
I hope you guys enjoy all the performance... um... yeah, this whole stream.
I hope you guys enjoyed all the performances... um... yeah, this whole stream.
みんな、ナイスキー！ Thank you for your birthday wishes! 後で読んであげますね。
Everyone, nice key! Thank you for your birthday wishes! I'll read them later.
バイバイ、みんな！ No more encore! No more encore! バイバイ！
Bye-bye, everyone! No more encore! No more encore! Bye-bye!
こぼこぼこぼ、こぼ・かなえる at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Kobo-kobo-kobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
Thank you! I can't be as bright as now Without you! - Kobo